Hey, my name is Rose Radford and I am a business strategist and wealth coach to
female entrepreneurs
and any woman who wants to make more money. I am so thrilled that I've been
asked to
create this short intro video for you so that you can have a bit of a taste of
the sort of work
that I do with my clients. The women, the incredible women of the world who are
crafting their own
parks by choosing to create income in their own unique way. Now, a lot of what
I support my clients
on is around creating a wealth mindset, a really good, healthy money mindset so
that they can
attract and steward more money for their own greater good to support them and
others in their
life. So what I'm about to share with you here is a short live video that I did
recently that
walks you through what a money block is. I'm not going to tell you what it is
just yet because
you're going to find out in a moment but this video also walks you through a
very short exercise that
helps you identify exactly what is holding you back from creating more income
and having more
financial wealth in your life right now. So with no further ado, I will hand
over to the pre-recorded
video and I will see you in a moment. A money block is simply any belief, fear
or action that is
standing in the way between you and your income goal or you receiving and
having more financial
wealth. So anything that's kind of as a bit of a block, a bit of a barrier in
front of you and
that can be a belief, fear or action. And I also like to use the term wealth
consciousness when it
comes to money to describe the relationship you have with money and abundance
in general in all
parts of your life. So having a really good wealth consciousness is really
about aligning yourself
so your beliefs, your thoughts, your emotions, your actions with financial
wealth as well as
other areas, other wealth across other areas of your life as well. So things
like relationships,
health, where you live, feeling abundant in where you live as well so that you
can live in a world
of more personal overflow in lots of different areas of abundance and really
become an abundance
attractor. Someone whose natural state is to attract financial overflow,
attract resources,
attract all types of abundance, joy, love into their life. And to do that, to
become an abundance
attractor, it's all about doing that inner wealth work yourself. Because you
don't create, you don't
have what you want, you create and have who you are. So it's really about
making those internal
shifts, which is why we're talking about money blocks today. Because money
blocks, as I said,
is one of those things, one of those beliefs or emotions that you have that
really holds you back
from being an abundance attractor by default. So are we ready to identify your
money blocks
right now? You might want to grab a pen and paper for this or grab your phone
and journal away in
your phone. So the first thing I want you to do is right now write down your
income goal that you
have at the moment. So this might be your income goal for the month. So write
it down and get really
clear about how much that is. You might set your income goals quarterly or
annually. So if that's
the case, then write that down instead. And we need to get really clear on what
that income
goal is a moment. If you can't write a goal down, that's a really interesting
feedback from the
beginning, because not having income goals can really sabotage you as well,
because you don't know
what you're working towards. If you're not declaring what you desire, then it
ain't going to come
very easily. You've got to state what you really desire, otherwise the universe
can't deliver it,
can it? So the second step then is to make this one assumption and then answer
these four questions.
So I hope you're all with me, pan and paper. So assuming that if you really
wanted it,
you'd already have it right now, why don't you actually want it? Why don't you
actually want that
10k month, let's say, or 50k month? Why do you not actually want that amount of
money, that income
goal? And we'd really listen and get curious, be patient with yourself, because
you might be
screaming back at me right now, because I want it rose, don't be ridiculous, of
course I want that
money. I set that goal for a reason, there's no reason why I don't want it, but
play the game.
And as I said, if you really wanted it, you'd already have it by now. So what
part of you doesn't
actually want it? So any reason for why you might not want that money? The next
question is then,
what's scary about having that income goal, having that income come in? If I
was to give you
that money right now, would that be scary? Any reason for that might be scary?
Any fear that
comes up? I often hear people say to me at this stage, that they're kind of
worried about what
happens taxes-wise, they're not sure about that. Sometimes people will say, I'm
not sure even what
I do with that amount of money, that's kind of scary to me. So really, we need
to be patient,
listen and get curious and write anything that comes down, comes up for you and
write it down.
Also, next question, what's not possible about your income goal? What part of
you is saying,
yeah, great income goal, but that's not going to happen, Rose. What's not going
to happen, Claire?
Or it's not going to happen, Sarah. What's that little voice telling you,
when it's saying that it's not really possible? What belief is screaming right
back at you,
that saying that your income goal is actually completely impossible. I don't
know why you've
reset it in the first place. I want you to get really, really clear on that.
What's the story
of telling yourself for why that income goal ain't possible? And then finally,
the last question
that I found so helpful in identifying your money blocks is, what's the worst
thing about having
that amount of money come in? What's the worst thing about that? Is it that
maybe you're scared
people are going to ask you for that money because they're going to see you are
able to make so much
money in your business and now friends and family are going to be wanting some
from you?
Is it that maybe you don't know how to manage it? It feels overwhelming. Is it
that you're worried
you're going to spend it all? What's coming up for you? Feel free to share if
you want to share,
of course, but absolutely no need to. Now, hopefully you've done that exercise
and in front of you,
all that piece of paper is going to be at least one of your current money
blocks.
These beliefs and fears are standing in the way between where you are now and
the financial
abundance that you desire in your business. And as I said, be patient and
curious. You might not
have the answer come out straight away right now. It might be percolating in
your brain in the
next few days if so, just listen. And here's the funny thing. I didn't think I
had any money blocks,
but I first started my business. The story I was telling myself was I'm great
with money.
I know how to make money. I can do that. I know how to manage money. I'm really
confident about it.
But the truth is your reality speaks louder than your reluctant and stubborn
subconscious
who doesn't want to hand over the limiting beliefs. So if you're in that same
position as me right
now and you've just told yourself, I have fabulous beliefs around money. My
parents modeled excellent
money management. I believe I commit lots of money. You might want to check it
on that.
Because to be honest, if you haven't done this work on your relationship with
money,
you are leaving thousands, if not millions, on the table over your lifetime.
This is this work,
this inner wealth work is necessary. I would say for everybody, absolutely
necessary.
So for me, I'll give you an example of one of the things that I shifted. When I
was doing this
work back last year, before last, one of the big things I realised was that I
believe I have to
work really hard for money. I come from a long line of miners, farmers, who
else, people just
work just working really, really hard in terms of parents and grandparents and
great grandparents.
And you probably come from a long line of very hard workers as well. And the
industrial age
taught us that the longer you work in the factory, the longer you work on the
farm,
the more money you'll make because there's more output being created. That's
where a lot of that
belief comes from. But the world is different now. You don't have to be sitting
in a factory to
create output to get paid good money for it. We live in a digital age. We live
in the information
age where you can make money really passively, really easily online, for
instance, as a starting
point. So when I identified this limiting belief, I have to work hard to make
money. I realised that
I was genuinely working really hard for the money I was making, far harder than
I needed to. So I
decided to shift that belief. And I decided to believe that money comes easily
to me. There's
money comes effortlessly to me. Can't get the word out. And I decided to
believe that money
worked differently for me. And literally three or four weeks later, after
shifting this belief,
an opportunity came in for me to be paid more than I've ever been paid before
for doing the least
amount of work I've ever done before. And I knew at that stage, that's in that
particular moment
that I had done that in a work to be able to attract opportunity. That
opportunity wouldn't have come
anywhere near me and my subconscious that was so dedicated to the belief that I
had to work hard
to make money. So this belief work ain't funny business. It is real and it
creates new opportunities
for you and allows you to attract abundance so much easier without needing to
necessarily work
really hard for it or be where he against yourself the whole time. Building a
business where you
feel as though money is hard or you only ever live in just enough mode or you
don't trust yourself
with money, all of that resistance, all of that money shit that's in your way,
that's going to
make building a business really, really hard. And we don't want that. We prefer
it to be slightly
easier. So some really common money blocks that I hear are things like I am
worried that I will
be perceived as being wrong or bad because if I make too much money, we know
that rich people
are typically perceived as being greedy. They might feel sometimes guilty about
having so much money
compared to others. And of course, so much money is different to everybody.
What's a lot of money
is different to everyone. It's all on a scale. A lot of people also believe
that to make really
good money in their business, it's got to come at a cost, a cost to their
health, a cost to their
relationships, a cost to working hard maybe, a cost to people not liking you.
And also as everybody
touched on being scared, fear comes up a lot with money where it's a fear of
judgment from others,
fear of taxes, fear of losing it all, fear of managing it, all of the above.
Money blocks are
are many. So what do you do with them? You essentially rewrite the story and
allow yourself to create
a new reality for yourself, as I said. The funny thing is, some people doubt
that you can actually
change your financial reality by simply changing your beliefs. But in response
to that, those people
miss the fact that those just getting by with money right now and those that
live in overflow
financially have entirely different belief systems and thoughts about money. A
great book to read on
this would be, I think it's called the millionaire mindset or something, where
he literally goes through
like 30 different beliefs and he compares people that don't have much money and
what they believe
about that particular topic around money and then the belief that wealthy
people have around that
topic with money. And you can see literally left to right and complete
comparison over how these
people think differently and they have completely different financial
situations. So if you feel
as if you're doubting that just changing your belief can change your reality,
just go read that
book and it'll blow your mind.